# Drashti Bharti - Technical Writer

Brampton, ON | drashtincs@gmail.com | /in/drashti-bharti | /dbharti-TW/dbharti TW portfolio | +1 (437) 599 3096

## **Career Summary**

Audience-centric technical writer with 6+ years of experience in documenting SaaS products in an agile environment. Effective communicator with knack for planning and simplifying complex technical tasks. Proven ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously, delivering within planned timelines and without compromising quality.

#### **Skills**

Technical Skills: Software Documentation, API Documentation, Information Architecture

IT Concepts and Tools: GitHub, Salesforce, Atlassian Jira, HTML, CSS, Java, C, OpenAPI Specifications

Documentation Tools: Atlassian Confluence, Microsoft Visual Studio Code, Swagger Editor, Microsoft Word

### **Experience**

#### Technical Writer II, Boston Scientific – Mississauga, Ontario

04/2023 - 12/2024

- Tested template migration process, recorded areas of improvement and template breaking solutions reducing process adaption time by 20%.
- Migrated over 250 documents into new template, incorporating information classification and new style.
- Processed 23 change request in Windchill, updating 350 manufacturing documents across 10 products through formal reviews and approvals from stakeholders while adhering to SOPs and industry standards.
- Created a checklist aiding writers and reviewers preparing documentation for change process, reducing recalls by 40%.

#### **Technical Writer,** Conga – Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

07/2018 - 02/2023

- Managed multiple enterprise products for 18+ releases independently or with team, delivering customer-facing administrator, user, and API reference guides with release notes through Confluence.
- Incorporated doc-as-code approach for company's developer hub hosted on Readme.io through GitHub. Collaborated with product and engineering managers, QAs, dev, and tech writers to streamline the technical process.
- Documented approximately 10 REST APIs with over 100 endpoints by adding inline description using Visual Studio Code and Swagger Editor to edit the YAML or JSON files.
- Established templates to document SOAP APIs and callbacks by gathering information from cross-functional teams and analyzing architecture. Documented over 150 SOAP APIs and 27 callbacks with proper sample codes.
- Refined and implemented release notes documentation and publication process by leveraging expertise developed by documenting over 210 release notes.

# **Special Projects**

Project Green Conga

Improved legacy content in Conga CPQ documentation based on feedback gathered from subject matter experts by rewriting content and reorganizing information hierarchy. Verified documentation by following it line-by-line and executing each functionality in sandbox. Defined review and approval criteria for stakeholders to ensure accuracy and adequacy of the content.

Call with Customer Conga

Resolved customer grievances by assisting Customer Success Manager. Presented viable solutions drawn from detailed audit of documentation and Jira to the customers directly. Demonstrated the documentation structure for their understanding.

Best Practices Guide Conga

Curated a guide to document best practices and guardrails of configuring Conga CPQ within Salesforce governor limits. Gathered information in various formats from engineers, architectures, QA, and professional services teams. Created content strategy and information architecture by analyzing the data. Conducting extensive reviews with subject matter experts.

# **Education**

Dhirubhai Ambani Institute of Information and Communication Technology, India –

B. Tech: Information And Communication Technology (ICT) 2014 – 2018